A Guide to the Office of the Vice President and Provost, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, [1978] 1982-1983 [1985]
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Vice President and Provost, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files [1978] 1982-1983 [1985]
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-3/1/2.871
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1987 April 8.
Contents List
- SERIES I: Topical Files
  - Academic Computing 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Academic Computing Computer Priority Committee 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Academic Space Administrator 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Committees 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Admissions (2 folders) 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action--Equal Employment Opportunities Office (1 of 3) 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action--Equal Employment Opportunities (2-3 of 3) 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action--SHEV 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - AAUP--General 1972-1983 (Box 2)
  - American Council on Education 1981-1983 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Universities 1978-1984 (Box 2)
  - Athletics, Department of 1978-1983 (Box 2)
  - Audits, Director of 1980-1983 (Box 2)
  - Bayly Museum 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Bayly Museum 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Birdwood 1977-1983 (Box 3)
  - Blandy Farm 1977-1983 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors (2 folders) 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Biennial Budget 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - --General (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - --General 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Budget Office--General 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - --Capital Outlay Budget 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - --Operating Budget 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - --Operating Budget (2 folders) 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - --Physical Planning 1980-1982 (Box 4)
  - Budget--Special Projects 1981-1984 (Box 5)
  - Bursar's Office 1973-1983 (Box 5)
  - Business and Finance, Vice President for [1977]1980-1983 (Box 5)
  - Calendar Committee [1981]1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Career Planning 1980-1983 (Box 5)
  - Census Reports & Enrollment Projection (2 folders) 1982-1984[1985] (Box 5)
  - Center for Advanced Studies 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Center for South Asian Studies (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Center & Institutes 1969-1983 (Box 6)
  - Central Virginia Consortium for Higher Education (2 folders) 1977-1983 (Box 6)
  - Chairs 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Clinch Valley College Materials (3 folders) 1979-1982 (Box 7)
  - Clinical Psychology Institute 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Committee Definitions [1971]1978-1979[1981] (Box 7)
  - Consortia for Continuing Education 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Dean's Meetings (3 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Dean's Meetings 1983-1984 (Box 8)
  - Dean's, Memos to 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Development--General (2 folders) 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - Development--Campaign Steering Committee [1982]1983-1985 (Box 8)
  - Downing College Fellowship Program (2 folders) 1982-19843 (Box 8)
  - Environmental Health and Safety Office 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Faculty--New Positions (1 of 2) 1979-1983 (Box 8)
  - --New Positions (2 of 2) 1979-1983 (Box 9)
  - --Faculty Forms--Revisions 1980-1982 (Box 9)
  - --Faculty Salaries 1982 (Box 9)
  - --Faculty Salaries 1983[1984] (Box 9)
  - --Faculty Senate 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - --Faculty Senate--Program Evaluation Committee (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Fellowship/Scholarships--General 1980-1984 (Box 9)
  - --Bunting 1981-1984 (Box 10)
  - --Commonwealth Faculty 1979-1983 (Box 10)
  - --Guggenheim 1979-1984 (Box 10)
  - --Kellogg 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Folger Institute 1979-1983 (Box 10)
  - Foundations--General 1972-1983 (Box 10)
  - Gifts/Grants [1977]1979-1983 (Box 10)
  - Governmental Relations 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office--Freeze 1982 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Action Teams (2 folders) 1982-1984 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Speeches 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Guest Houses--Morea 1979-1983 (Box 11)
  - Health Affairs, Vice President for 1978-1983 (Box 11)
  - Indirect Costs 1979-1983 (Box 11)
  - Information Technology, Department of 1982-1984 (Box 11)
  - Institute of Government 1979-1983 (Box 11)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies 1983 (Box 11)
  - International Student Affairs 1979-1983 (Box 12)
  - Libraries--General [1975]1983 (Box 12)
  - Madison Hall Renovations 1982-1985 (Box 12)
  - Madison, The Papers of James 1979-1983 (Box 12)
  - Materiel Management Search Committee 1980-1983 (Box 12)
  - National Association of State University and Land Grant Colleges 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Personnel 1983 (Box 12)
  - Physical Plant 1982 (Box 13)
  - Physical Plant --Apprenticeship Program 1983 (Box 13)
  - Physical Plant --Planning Assumption (2 folders) 1981-1982 (Box 13)
  - Physical Plant --Planning--Garrett Hall Renovation 1981-1982 (Box 13)
  - President's Office--General Correspondence 1983-1984[1985] (Box 13)
  - Promotion and Tenure (2 folders) 1982-1984 (Box 13)
  - Promotion and Tenure--Outside Tenure Appointments (2 folders) [1980]1982-1984 (Box 13)
  - Provost, Office of the 1983 (Box 13)
  - Provost Advisory Committee [1981]1982 (Box 13)
  - Provost Advisory Committee [1982]1983 (Box 14)
  - Provost--Associate Provost for Academic Support 1981-1982 (Box 14)
  - Provost--Associate Provost for Research (2 folders) 1983 (Box 14)
  - Science & Technology, Governor's Task Force on (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Southern Association of Colleges & Schools (1 of 2) 1980-1982 (Box 14)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (2 of 2) 1980-1982 (Box 15)
  - SURA [Southeastern Universities Research Association, Inc.] (3 folders) 1983 (Box 15)
  - Summer Session (1 of 2) 1982 (Box 15)
  - Summer Session (2 of 2) 1982 (Box 16)
  - Summer Session 1983 (Box 16)
  - Vice Presidential Planning Group (4 folders) 1982-1983[1984] (Box 16)
  - Vice Presidential Planning Group 1984[1986] (Box 17)
  - Virginia House 1982 (Box 17)
  - Visiting Committee 1977-1980 (Box 17)
  - Washington Papers 1979-1983 (Box 17)
  - Weedon Foundation 1979-1984 (Box 17)
- SERIES II: School Files
  - Architecture School 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Arts & Sciences, Faculty of 1982 (Box 18)
  - Graduate Arts & Sciences 1982 (Box 18)
  - Arts & Sciences, Faculty of 1983 (Box 18)
  - Graduate Arts & Sciences 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Arts & Sciences, College of 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Afro-American Studies 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Art Department 1982-1984 (Box 18)
  - Biology Department 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Government & Foreign Affairs Department 1982-1984 (Box 18)
  - Commerce 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Continuing Education School (3 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - Darden School (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - Education School (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - Engineering School (3 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - --CIT (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - --Graduate TV Program [1982]-1983 (Box 20)
  - --Graduate TV Program 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Law School (3 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Medicine, School of 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Nursing School 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - SHEV--Academic Common Market--General Correspondence (2 folders) [1973]1984 (Box 21)
  - --Excellence Correspondence 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - --Excellence Proposals 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - --Excellence Graduate Recruitment Program 1983-1985 (Box 22)
  - --Excellence Minority Recruitment and Retention [1982]1983[1984] (Box 22)
  - --General (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - --IPAC 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - --New Degree Programs 1982-1983 (Box 22)
- SERIES III: Biennial Planning Files
  - Sesqui Applications--Anthropology 1983-1986 (Box 23)
  - --Astronomy 1984 (Box 23)
  - --Art 1984 (Box 23)
  - --Chemistry 1984 (Box 23)
  - --Classics 1984 (Box 23)
  - --Drama 1984 (Box 23)
  - --Economics 1984 (Box 23)
  - --Engineering (2 folders) 1984-1986 (Box 23)
  - --English 1984 (Box 23)
  - --French 1984 (Box 23)
  - --Government & Foreign Affairs 1984 (Box 23)
  - --History 1984 (Box 23)
  - --Mathematics 1984-1986 (Box 23)
  - --Music 1984-1986 (Box 23)
  - --Oriental Languages 1984-1986 (Box 23)
  - --Physics 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - --Psychology 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - --Religious Studies 1984 (Box 24)
  - --Slavic 1984 (Box 24)
  - --Sociology 1984 (Box 24)
  - --Spanish, Italian and Portuguese 1984 (Box 24)
  - --Law 1983-1984 (Box 24)
  - Sesqui--General (2 folders) [1978]1979-1981[1982] (Box 24)
  - --Miscellaneous 1969-1976 (Box 24)
  - --Reports [1979]1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - --Reports 1980-1981[1983] (Box 24)
  - --Proposals [1978]1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - --Proposals [1979]1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - --Proposal--O. Whitfield Broom, Jr. 1981-1983 (Box 24)
  - --Proposal--Robert S. Kemp [1984]1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - --Proposal--Andy Ruppel 1984[1985-1986] (Box 24)
  - Annual Report--Arts & Sciences (2 folders) 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - --Arts & Sciences (2 folders) 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - --Arts & Sciences (2 folders) 1980-1981 (Box 25)
  - --Commerce, McIntire School of 1978-1981 (Box 26)
  - --Commerce, McIntire School of 1979-1980 (Box 26)
  - --Darden School 1978-1980 (Box 26)
  - --Education, School of 1978-1980 (Box 26)
  - --Continuing Education, Division of 1978-1980[1983] (Box 26)
  - --Engineering & Applied Science, School of 1978-1979 (Box 26)
  - --Engineering & Applied Science, School of 1979-1981 (Box 27)
  - --Nursing, School of 1978-1979 (Box 27)
  - --Clinical Psychology, Institute of 1980-1983 (Box 27)
  - --Law, Psychiatry and Public Policy, Institute of 1982-1983 (Box 27)
  - --Law, School of (2 folders) 1976-1977 (Box 27)
  - --Law, School of (2 folders) 1977-1978 (Box 28)
  - --Claude Moore Health Sciences Library, The 1980-1984 (Box 28)
  - --University of Virginia Library 1978-1979 (Box 28)
  - --Physical Plant, Department of 1980-1984 (Box 28)
- Series IV: Restricted Files (Box Boxes 29-31)